D2.
Read Amy's proposal on protecting the ocean.
Dear Sir or Madam, I am writing today to ask for your help in protecting the ocean.
The ocean is home to many kinds of sea life.
It provides us with food and offers us space to have fun.
However, the ocean is facing many problems.
Pollution is one of the biggest problems.
There are millions of tons of plastic waste in the ocean.
Also, waste water from factories and houses travels to the ocean and causes pollution.
This will harm or even kill sea life.
We can help solve the problems.
We should keep beaches clean and use more environment-friendly products.
It is also a good idea to tell people how to protect the ocean.
We can also encourage them to help.
It is meaningful to join an environmental group and workers a volunteer.
Please join us.
Together, we can help protect the ocean.
With kind thanks, Zhao Min.